In this video we will show you how to prepare your
このビデオにより iOS アプリケーションで
iOS application on iTunes Connect for publishing.
iTunes Connect によりパブリッシュするための準備をみていきます。
Open Manage Your Applications.
Manage Your Applications を開きます。
In there you will see all your mobile and standalone applications.
この中で全てのモバイル、スタンドアローンのアプリケーションを確認できます。
Let's start and add a new application by clicking
はじめに新規のアプリケーションを追加するために
Add New App.
Add New App をクリックします。
Here you will need to select iOS or OS X Application.
ここでは iOS or OS X アプリケーションを選択します。
Select iOS.
iOS を選択します。
Here you will need to write your primary
ここでは アプリケーションに関する主な情報を
information about your app.
書く必要があります。
Write the app name, this is the title of your game or app.
App Name はゲームまたはアプリケーションのタイトルです。
Enter the SKU number.
SKU Number を入力します。
Select a bundle ID, which you've created in your
developer.apple.com のアカウントで作成した
Developer.Apple.Com account.
Bundle ID を選択します。
Enter the bundle ID suffix,
Bundle ID Suffix を入力します。
which should be named the same as you entered
これは Unity の iOS Player Settings の Bundle Identifier で
in your iOS Player Settings bundle identifier in Unity.
入力したものと同じネーミングにします。
After you finish, click continue.
完了した後は、Continue をクリックします。
In this step select your application availability date and price.
このステップでは アプリケーションの Availability Date および Price を選択します。
Select continue.
Continue を選択します。
In this step we will need to write all the details about the application,
このステップではアプリケーションに関するすべての詳細について書く必要があり、
enter the version number.
Version Number を入力します。
It should be exactly as you wrote in Unity's
これは Unity の iOS Player Settings Version にて
iOS Player Settings Version.
書いたものと全く同様とすべきです。
Enter the copyright,
Copyright を入力します。
it's your company, studio or team name.
これは 企業名、スタジオ名、またはチーム名です。
Select the primary category and sub-category.
Primary Category および Sub Category を選択します。
Select a secondary category if required.
必要な場合にかぎり Secondary Category を選択します。
Next go through the rating system.
次に Rating に進みます。
Next meta data, enter a short description of your game.
次は Metadata です。ゲームに短い紹介文を入力します。
Enter search keywords by which your game
ストアでゲームをみつけるときの
will be found on the store.
検索に使う Keywords を入力します。
Enter a support URL or other information if required.
Support URL および他の情報を必要であれば入力します。
In contact information enter your
Contact Inforamtion の中では
first and last names, an email address and a phone number.
First name, Last Name, Email address および Phone Number を入力します。
Don't worry about these optional fields now,
この時点ではオプションで用意されているフィールドは無視して下さい。
you can enter them later if required.
必要であれば後で入力できます。
Regarding uploads, the minimum requirements
Uploads に関して、最小の要件は
are to upload an icon of 1024 pixels squared
1024 x 1024 ピクセルのアイコンおよび
and one of any of your screen shots.
スクリーンショットのどれかををアップロードすることです。
The rest of the screen shots you can upload later.
残りのスクリーンショットは後からアップロードできます。
Screen shots should match the screen size that you've chosen.
スクリーンショットは選択したスクリーンサイズと一致すべきです。
And the upload quality should be as good as possible.
そしてアップロード品質はできるかなり良いものにすべきです。
After you finish click save.
完了した後は Save をクリックします。
If everything that you wrote and selected is correct,
もし 書いて選択した内容の全てが正しければ、
you will see your application status is now
アプリケーションお Status は
'Prepared For Upload'.
Prepared for Upload となります。
If you go back to Manage Your Apps
もし Manage Your Apps に戻ると
you will see that your application is now in the list.
アプリケーションが今度はリストに表示されていることが確認できます。
If you want to add more details, or change something,
もしより詳細を追加したい、または何かを変更したい場合、
you can click on your app, select View Details
アプリケーションをクリックして、 View Details を選択して
and change the majority of the information.
情報の大部分を変更することが出来ます。
You can change that any time
これはいつでも変更できるので
so don't worry if you're not sure if you wrote everything correctly.
すべてが正しいかどうか自信がない場合も心配する必要はありません。
If everything is okay and you're ready to upload the game binary
もし全て問題がなく、ゲームのバイナリをアップロードする準備ができた場合、
click on Ready To Upload Binary.
Ready をクリックしてバイナリをアップロードして下さい。
Answer Yes or No to the question about encryption,
暗号化（Encryption） に関する質問には Yes または No を選択したうえで
click Save and then Continue.
Save をクリックして続けます。
You will now see that your application has changed status
アプリケーションの Status に変更が加えられ、
from Ready To Upload to Waiting For Upload.
Ready To Upload から Waitinf For Upload になったことが確認できます。
That means that the application preparation part is done.
これはつまりアプリケーションの準備部分が完了したことを意味します。
You can now upload your binary through Xcode
これでバイナリを Xcode とおしてアップロードすることが出来るので、
and we'll cover how to do that next.
次にそのやり方をみていきます。
Now that you've prepared your application on
iTunes Connect でのアプリケーションを
iTunes Connect for upload it's time to prepare your
アップロードする準備が出来たので、今度は
application and content in Unity and send it to Xcode.
アプリケーションおよびコンテンツを Unity で準備して Xcode に送信します。
Open the build settings in the editor.
エディタで Build Settings を開きます。
Go to File - Build Settings.
File - Build Settings を選択して
Make sure that the iOS platform is selected
iOS プラットフォームが選択されていることを確認して、
and make sure that your scenes are included.
シーンが含まれているか確認します。
Click on player settings and check if
Player Settings をクリックして
in Cross Platform settings you wrote Company Name.
Cross-Platform Settings にて Company Name を入力したか確認します。
It should be your company name as you wrote
これは iTunes Connect で書いた
in iTunes Connect.
Company Name と同様であるべきです。
Check also that you've written the product name,
Product Name を入力したことも確認します。
this will be the exact name of your application label on the device.
これはデバイス上のアプリケーションのタイトル名として、そのまま表示されます。
Check that the default icon is selected.
Default Icon が選択されていることを確認します。
In resolution and presentation that the default resolution is correct,
Resolution および Presentation において、デフォルトの解像度および
and the status bar is correct for you.
Status Bar が正しいことを確認します。
In icon, the 'All Icons' will be selected as your default icon.
Icon では、デフォルトアイコンとして All Icons が選択されます。
If you want to override a specific icon for a specific resolution
もし特定の解像度で特定のアイコンを上書きしたい場合は、
you can change it by checking Override For iPhone.
Override For iPhone をチェックすることで変更することが出来ます。
In Splash Image check that you have added
Splash Image では すべての必要なスプラッシュ画面を追加したか
all required splash screens.
確認します。
If you application is only for iPhone or iPad
もしアプリケーションが iPhone または iPad 向けのみの場合、
you can only add them.
追加することしか出来ません。
Otherwise you will need to add all of them.
そうでなければすべてを追加する必要があります。
In Other Settings check if your bundle identifier
Other Settings では Bundle Identifier が
is named exactly as it is in iTunes Connect.
iTunes Connect と全く同様の名前になっているか確認します。
It has to be 100% exact.
これは 100% 一致している必要があります。
This is also true for bundle version.
これは Bundle Version についても同じことがいえます。
Check all other important settings like
他のすべての重要な設定も確認します。
Target Device, SDK version and Stripping Level.
例えば、Target Device, SDK version および Stripping Level などです。
When your Player Settings are setup
Player Settings がセットアップできたら
go back to Build Settings.
Build Settings に戻ります。
Check if Sym Link Unity Libraries and Development Build
Sym Link Unity Libraries と Development Build
is checked.
がチェックされていないか確認します。
If not, click build.
チェックされてなければ、Build ボタンをクリックします。
Give a name for your Xcode project and click save.
Xcode プロジェクトに名前をつけて Save をクリックします。
Wait for it to finish compiling.
コンパイルが終わるのを待ちます。
When it finishes Unity will open a Finder window
完了した後、Unity は Finder ウィンドウを開いて
and your Xcode project will appear.
Xcode プロジェクトが表示されます。
In the next part we will show you how to proceed
次のパートでは、アプリケーションを
with uploading your application from
Xcode からiTunes Connect に
Xcode to iTunes Connect.
アップロードする方法をみていきます。
In this final part we will show you how to
この最後のパートでは、
submit your Unity application from Xcode.
Xcode から Unity アプリケーションを提出する方法をみていきます。
Once you've built your application from Unity
Unity からアプリケーションをビルドした後は
open the Xcode project.
Xcode プロジェクトを開きます。
When Xcode launches, clean the project by going to
Xcode がローンチされたら
Product - Clean.
Product - Clean のメニューによりプロジェクトをクリーンアップします。
Select Issue Navigator, the triangle with the
! 記号が中に含まれる黄色い三角形アイコンの
exclamatory mark inside, and select your project.
Issue Navigator を選択して、プロジェクトを選択します。
In the Summary tab check if all the settings
Summary タブでは全ての設定が
are set correctly from Unity.
Unity から正しくセットされている確認します。
In Build Settings tab you will need to change
Build Settings タブではコード署名（Code Signing）を
your code signing from Developer to Distribution.
Developer から Distribution に変更する必要があります。
Before that we suggest you run your application
これを行なう前に、最後にもう一回
one more time on the device to double check
デバイス上ですべて問題ないかダブルチェックすることを
that everything's okay.
推奨します。
When you change code signing to distribution
Code Signing を Distribution に変更するとき
perform Clean one more time.
もう一回 Clean を実行します。
Then build for archiving by clicking
次にアーカイブビルドするために
Product - Build For - Archiving.
メニューから Product - Build For - Archiving をクリックします。
It will build your application for distribution.
これによりアプリケーションは配布用にビルドされます。
Then you will need to archive it by clicking
次にアーカイブするために
Product - Archive.
メニューから Product - Archive をクリックします。
Wait for it to finish
完了するのを待って
and after archiving is successful Xcode will
そしてアーカイブが無事完了した後、Xcode は
open the organiser automatically.
自動的にオーガナイザを開きます。
In the organise click Distribute.
オーガナイザの中で Distribute をクリックします。
Click Next.
次に Next をクリックします。
Put your login information and click Next again.
ログイン情報を入力して、再び Next をクリックします。
Choose your application which is on iTunes Connect.
iTunes Connect にあるアプリケーションを選択します。
Select code signing identity and click Next.
Code Signing Identity を選択して Next をクリックします。
Now Xcode will check your application binary
これで Xcode はアプリケーション バイナリに間違いがないか
for any mistakes.
チェックします。
Splash screens, icon, SDK, targets etcetera.
Splash screens, icon, SDK, targets などをみます。
It might take a few minutes.
数分かかることがあります。
When it finishes checking it should say
完了した後は、
'no issues were found in your application'.
no issues were found in your application と表示されるはずです。
Now open the iTunes Connect page and refresh the page.
次に iTunes Connect のページを開いてページを更新します。
You will see that your application status is now Upload Received.
アプリケーションの Status が Upload Received になったことを確認できます。
iTunes Connect might ask you for some more information
iTunes Connect では
like Add All Necessary Screen Shots or similar.
Add All Necessary Screen Shots (必要なスクリーンショットを全て追加して下さい) などと情報を求めてくる可能性があります。
But now you are done and you should see your status change to
これで完了なので、Status は
Waiting For Review pretty soon.
しばらくすれば Waiting For Review となるはずです。
Then finally In Review, which may take 1 to 2 weeks.
そして、最終的には In Review となり、これは 1 - 2 週ほどかかります。
If everything is okay your application will be submitted
全て問題なければアプリケーションは
to the app store.
AppStore に提出されます。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)